(Sheldon:)And also, it's really scary.
(Leonard:)Would someone please turn off
the Sheldon commentary track?
(Sheldon:)There's no switch.
Just listen and learn.
(Howard:)Penny, if you think
this is good,
(Howard:)you should come with us Friday
(Howard:)to see it on the big screen
at the Colonial.
(Penny:)Well, I'm watching it now.
(Penny:)Why would I want to see it again
on Friday?
(Sheldon:)Because the print
they're showing on Friday
(Sheldon:)has an additional 21 seconds
of previously unseen footage.
(Penny:)21 seconds? That'll be like
seeing a whole new movie!
(Leonard:)Exactly.
(Leonard:)They say it finally solves
the submarine controversy.
(Sheldon:)Did-- Leonard?
(Sheldon:)I'm no expert, but I believe
(Sheldon:)what we just heard from Penny
was sarcasm.
Oh! Good.
(Sheldon:)I'm eight for 26 this month.
(Penny:)Yeah, I think I'll pass.
(Penny:)But you guys enjoy
your extra 21 seconds.
(Leonard:)Bet if I could
make you understand
(Leonard:)why this is such a cool thing,
we'd still be together.
(Penny:)Mm, yeah, no,
we wouldn't.
(Howard:)Uh-huh.
(Howard:)I'm guessing 21 seconds had
something to do with that, too.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪